Come on, it’s gon be fuckin’ hard
준비됐어? 장난 아닐거야
Special edition and your AI couldn’t copy
난 스페셜 에디션, 너의 AI도 날 복제 해내진 못했지
I’m leaving clues in the fitting room and it’s hot tea
피팅룸엔 흔적 남겨둬, 핫한 가십거리가 되겠지
No I’m not thinking ’bout no exes know they miss me
예전 애인들은 생각도 안나는데 날 생각할거야
I got the whole room spinning like it’s tipsy
이 곳 전체를 취한것 처럼 움직이게 만들었어
Don’t bore us take you to the chorus
지루하게 하지 말고 바로 후렴으로 가자
Whooooooo wanna rock with Jennie
누가 여기 제니와 놀아볼래
Keep your hair done, nails done like Jennie
머리부터 발끝까지 완벽하게, 마치 제니처럼
Who else got ‘em obsessed like Jennie
누가 제니처럼 빠져들게 할 수 있니?
Like like like
Jennie Jennie Jennie
제니 제니 제니
I think I really like
난 내 자신을 사랑해
Haters they don’t really like
못마땅하겠지, 그래 이해해
Cause they can never ever be
날 넘을 수 없다는 걸 알잖아
But have you ever met
근데 너, 진짜 날 본 적 있어?
Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie
제니 제니 제니 제니 제니
It’s Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie
난 제니 제니 제니 제니 제니
But have you ever met
너 진짜
근데 진짜
But have you ever met
정말로 진짜 본 적 있어?
얼말 줘도 못해 서커스짓
포징한번에 만들어 mosh pit
They can't deal with me cause I’m priceless
내 가치는 숫자로 못 매겨, 유일한 존재니까
여러 셀럽들 속에 내 DNA
Get get outta my way
비켜, 내 길에서 사라져
바비가 처키가 되기 전에
Name, shame, blame
특정하고, 망신주고, 비난하고
Tryna burst my bubble
내 기분을 나쁘게 하려고 해도
터트려봐 그럼 더 큰 홀에서
만나는 거야 제니를
Keep shading
계속 떠들어
예술작품엔 필요해 frame 이
예술 작품엔 필요해, 액자가
I’ve slayed it, and I graved it
난 해냈고, 내 흔적을 새겼어
Yes I'm guilty 잘난 게 죄니
그래, 난 유죄야. 잘난 게 죄니
Whooooooo wanna rock with Jennie
누가 여기 제니와 놀아볼래
Keep your hair done, nails done like Jennie
머리부터 발끝까지 완벽하게, 마치 제니처럼
Who else got ‘em obsessed like Jennie
누가 제니처럼 빠져들게 할 수 있니?
Like like like
I think I really like
난 내 자신을 사랑해
Haters they don’t really like Jennie
제니를 못마땅해 할 수도 있겠지
Cause they can never ever be Jennie
왜냐면 절대 제니가 될 수 없다는걸 아니까
But have you ever met
근데 너, 진짜 본 적 있어?
Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie
제니 제니 제니
It’s Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie
제니 제니 제니 제니
Like Jennie Jennie Jennie
제니 제니 제니
Jennie Jennie
제니 제니
Rock with Jennie
제니랑 놀자
Keep your hair done, nails done like Jennie
머리부터 발끝까지 완벽하게, 마치 제니처럼
Who else got ’em obsessed like
누가 제니처럼 빠져들게 할 수 있니?
But have you ever met Jennie
근제 진짜 제니 만나 봤어?
But have you ever met
근데 진짜로 만나봤어?
Jennie Jennie Jennie
제니 제니 제니
It’s Jennie Jennie Jennie Jennie
난 제니 제니 제니 제니